A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial, Bob Wands, Series 5 FA458
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial, Robert A. (Bob) Wands, Series 5
1958-1974
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller).
FA458
23 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
Box 1, 2, 3, and 30 are record cartons. Box 4, 5, 6, 7, and 24 are pamphlet boxes. Box 8, 13-17, 26-29 and 32 are flat boxes. Box 9, 10, 11, 21, 22 and 31 are letter size document boxes. Box 18-20 are legal size document boxes. Box 12 is a half letter size document boxes. Box 23, 25 and 33 are half legal size document boxes. Box 34 and 35 are microfiche boxes. Box 36 and 37 are wooden boxes.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Photographic negatives cannot be handled or viewed by researchers due to the fragile nature of the format. To request duplication of an image(s), please contact an Archivist.
File Plan note
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records are formerly classified as III 15.
Notations to RG 15 are used in this collection guide. If/when the notations in this guide are revised, an updated version of the guide will be made available for scholarly access.
Other Finding Aids
For other Nelson A. Rockefeller photographic holdings, please see the following finding aids:
FA454 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Nelson A. Rockefeller family, Series 1008
FA455 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Room 5600, Rockefeller family office, Series 2
FA456 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 3
FA457 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 4
FA459 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Vice Presidential, Series 6
FA460 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Unprocessed photographs, Series 7
Arrangement note
The Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs are arranged in the following series:
Series 1008: Nelson A. Rockefeller family. Series 2: Room 5600, Rockefeller family office. Series 3: Gubernatorial Press Office. Series 4: Gubernatorial Press Office. Series 5: Gubernatorial, Robert A. (Bob) Wands. Series 6: Vice Presidential. Series 7: Unprocessed photographs.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for scholarly research.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Arrangement note
Rockefeller family photographic holdings are arranged into the following series:
Rockefeller family and Avery family photographs, Series 1001. William Avery Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1002. John D. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1003. William Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1004. John D. Rockefeller Jr. family photographs, Series 1005. Pocantico Hills photographs, Series 1006. John D. Rockefeller 3rd family photographs, Series 1007. Nelson A. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1008. Laurance S. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1009. David Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1010.
Other Finding Aids note
For other Rockefeller family photographic holdings, please see the following finding aids:
FA445 Rockefeller family and Avery family photographs, Series 1001
FA446 William Avery Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1002
FA447 John D. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1003
FA448 William Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1004
FA449 John D. Rockefeller Jr. family photographs, Series 1005
FA450 Pocantico Hills photographs, Series 1006
FA451 John D. Rockefeller 3rd family photographs, Series 1007
FA452 Laurance S. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1009
FA453 David Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1010
Art, Modern; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1966; Arts; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1970; New York (N.Y.); New York (State); Political campaigns -- United States; Rockefeller family -- Art collections; State governments -- United States; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich); New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller).
- Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial, 1958-1974; 5
  - Prints, 1959-1964; Boxes 1-3 contain large prints. Boxes 4-7 contain small prints. Box 8 contains oversized prints.
    - Prints, 1959 June-December; D105-D206
      - 10-Mile River Boy Scout Camp (Monticello, NY), 1959 July 28; D105 (Box 1)
      - Limited Profit Housing Corp. (55th St.), 1959 September 21; D126 (Box 1)
      - Pulaski Day Parade (41 St. & 5th Ave.), 1959 October 4; D145 (Box 1)
      - Columbus Day Parade w/Carlino (62 St. & 5th Ave.), 1959 October 12; D154 (Box 1)
      - State Police Barracks Dedication (Albany, NY), 1959 October 27; D166 (Box 1)
      - Federation of Protestant Welfare Luncheon (Roosevelt - NY City), 1959 November 5; D170 (Box 1)
      - American Legion - National Commander Martin B. McKneally (55th St.), 1959 November 19; D177 (Box 1)
      - Seven State Trip (Dallas, TX), 1959 December 17; D206 (Box 1)
    - Prints, 1960 January-December; D2000-D2644
      - Negro Soldier at Mansion (Albany), 1960 January 1; D2000 (Box 1)
      - American Helenic Societies of Greater NY Reception - Archbishop Iacovas, Mr. Root Spyros Skouras (10 E 79th St.), 1960 January 21; D2001 (Box 1)
      - Governor speaks to legislature (Albany), 1960 January 21; D2002 (Box 1)
      - Insurance Department Centennial (Commodore), 1960 January 21; D2003 (Box 1)
      - Fireman (Roosevelt), 1960 January 21; D2003A (Box 1)
      - Westchester Republican County Committee Dinner - Drop In (Commodore), 1960 Janury 21; D2004 (Box 1)
      - Israeli Ambassador (55th St.), 1960 January 22; D2005 (Box 1)
      - Carlino, Meyner, Rubicoff (55th St.), D2006 (Box 1)
      - Baseball Writers Dinner (Astor), 1960 January 31; D2007 (Box 1)
      - Osteopathic Society Luncheon (Waldorf), 1960 February 10; D2009 (Box 1)
      - Minister of Ghana (55th St.), D2010 (Box 1)
      - Eye Bank Girl (55th St.), 1960 February 25; D2011 (Box 1)
      - Monitor Taping, D2011A (Box 1)
      - Fallout Shelter - Savings Bank 6th Ave. (49th St. - NY City), D2012 (Box 1)
      - Conservation Meeting (Music Hall), D2013 (Box 1)
      - "Today" Show - NBC - Fallout Shelter - Dave Garroway (NBC - Studio 3), 1960 March 4; D2014 (Box 1)
      - YWCA National Board - NY City (600 Lex. Ave.), 1960 March 3; D2015 (Box 1)
      - Commissioner McHugh "Fallout Shelter" Program (Roosevelt), 1960 March 4; D2016 (Box 1)
      - Malcolm Wilson's Birthday Party (55th St.), 1960 Febraury 26; D2017 (Box 1)
      - TV show - Job Opportunity (Red Room-Albany), 1960 March 10; D2018 (Box 1)
      - Dinner - United Jewish Appeal (Roosevelt), 1960 March 16; D2019 (Box 1)
      - St. Patrick's Day Parade (5th Ave & 63rd), 1960 March 17; D2020 (Box 1)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Mayor Press Conference (55th St), 1960 March 17; D2021 (Box 1)
      - Boys Town of Italy (55th St.), 1960 March 18; D2022 (Box 1)
      - Mental Health Group (55th St.), 1960 March 18; D2023 (Box 1)
      - Press Conference (Red Room-Albany), 1960 February 23; D2024 (Box 1)
      - Senator Austin's 50 years in government Celebration - Governor & Group (Conference Room-Albany), D2025 (Box 1)
      - TV show - Reorganization (Red Room-Albany), 1960 March 24; D2026 (Box 1)
      - CBS Show TV "The Great Challenge" (71st & York Ave.), 1960 March 27; D2027 (Box 1)
      - Press Conference (Red Room-Albany), 1960 March 29; D2028 (Box 1)
      - Legislative Session - last night (Albany), 1960 March 20; D2029 (Box 1)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Bill Signing (Red Room-Albany), 1960 April 7; D2030 (Box 1)
      - Jamestown Community College (Jamestown, NY), 1960 April 7; D2031 (Box 1)
      - Groundbreaking of State University College (Stony Brook, LI), 1960 April 8; D2033 (Box 1)
      - Bill Signing - 2 bills (55th St.), 1960 April 8; D2034 (Box 1)
      - Bill Signing - Urban League (55th St.), D2035 (Box 1)
      - Dinner for President and Mrs. Alberto Lieras Camargo of Cambodia (Knickerbocker Club), 1960 April 11; D2036 (Box 1)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller speaks at annual World Trade Council Pan American Day Luncheon sponsored by Chamber of Commerce (Rochester), 1960 April 13; D2038 (Box 1)
      - Peruvian Ambassador Fernando Berckemeyer, 1960 April 13; D2039 (Box 1)
      - Groundbreaking ceremonies at new Kordite Company Plant in Macedon (Macedon, NY), 1960 April 13; D2040 (Box 1)
      - Groundbreaking ceremonies at the Di-Noc Company of Cleveland Plant (Macedon, NY), 1960 April 13; D2041 (Box 1)
      - Mayor of Rochester Peter Barry summer home, D2042 (Box 1)
      - General Charles de Gaulle (Waldorf - NY City), 1960 April 26; D2043 (Box 1)
      - Bill Signing story (Albany), 1960 April 28; D2044 (Box 1)
      - (inclusive) Bill Signing story (Albany), 1960 April 29 (Box 1)
      - Wrap-up TV Show (Red Room-Albany), 1960 April 29; D2045 (Box 1)
      - Local 32B (Astor Hotel - NY City), 1960 May 2; D2046 (Box 1)
      - Israeli Independence (City Hall Plaza), 1960 May 2; D2047 (Box 1)
      - Groundbreaking - Fordham University (Lincoln Center - NY City), 1960 May 3; D2048 (Box 1)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Governor Quinn of Hawaii (55th St.), 1960 May 3; D2049 (Box 1)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Wm. Scranton of Pa.- Emmett Hughes (55th St.), 1960 May 3; D2050 (Box 1)
      - Civil Defense Briefing, Inspection (Peekskill Armory), 1960 May 4; D2051 (Box 1)
      - Willard State Hospital - Plaque (Ovid, NY), 1960 May 5; D2052 (Box 1)
      - NYS Agricultural Station - Cornell (Geneva, NY), 1960 May 5; D2053 (Box 1)
      - Japan Society (Hotel Pierre - NY City), 1960 May 23; D2055 (Box 1)
      - Press Conference (Red Room-Albany), 1960 May 25; D2057 (Box 1)
      - County Chairman Luncheon (Elmira, NY), 1960 May 26; D2060 (Box 1)
      - Automation Conference Dinner (Cooperstown, NY), 1960 June 1; D2063 (Box 1)
      - Trip to North Dakota (North Dakota), 1960 June 3-5; D2064 (Box 1)
      - UJA (56th St.), D2065 (Box 1)
      - Legion of Honor (French Embassy), 6/8/1960; D2066 (Box 1)
      - Roosevelt Hotel - Nelson A. Rockefeller Announcement (Roosevelt Hotel), 1960 June 8; D2067 (Box 1)
      - Anniversary Day Parade Sunday School Union (Brooklyn), 1960 June 9; D2068 (Box 1)
      - NMEX man, 1960 June 9; D2069 (Box 1)
      - CBS set-up (55th St.), 1960 June 9; D2070 (Box 1)
      - British Exhibition - Coliseum - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Prince Philip, VP Nixon (Coliseum - NY City), 1960 June 10; D2071 (Box 1)
      - AAA Safety Poster Awards (55th St.), 1960 June 13; D2072 (Box 1)
      - Hadassah Group & NY State Flag for Israel (55th St.), 1960 June 14; D2073 (Box 1)
      - Republican State Committee Luncheon (Commodore - NY City), 1960 June 14; D2074 (Box 1)
      - Dedication ceremonies, new basic science bldg. Roswell Park Memorial Institute (Buffalo, NY), 1960 June 17; D2075 (Box 1)
      - Rotary Luncheon (Binghamton), 1960 June 21; D2078 (Box 1)
      - William Hill Home (Union, NY), 1960 June 21; D2079 (Box 1)
      - Binghamton Flood (Binghamton), 1960 June 21; D2080 (Box 1)
      - Hill Dinner - Ukrainian Church (Binghamton), 1960 June 21; D2081 (Box 1)
      - Lake George Inn - dinner after viewing Conservation facilities (Lake Georges), 1960 June 22; D2082 (Box 1)
      - Whiteface Inn (Whiteface, NY), 1960 June 22; D2083 (Box 1)
      - Swear-In - Dorothea E. Donaldson-Unemployment Insurance Appeal Board Chair (55th St.), D2084B (Box 1)
      - Joseph Carlino Scholarship Dinner - Long Beach Republican Club (Lido Beach), 1960 June 30; D2085 (Box 1)
      - African-American Institute - Alhaji the Honorable Sir Ahmadu Bello-Sardauna of Sokoto, Premier of Northern Nigeria & Sir Mohammadu Sanusi, the Emir of Kano (Waldorf), 1960 July 6; D2086 (Box 1)
      - Henry Wheatley, Nelson A. Rockefeller and Dr. Ronan (55th St.), 1960 July 11; D2087 (Box 1)
      - Young Republicans' Luncheon (Vincent's Restaurant), 1960 July 12; D2088 (Box 1)
      - CBS Interview (55th St.), 1960 July 12; D2089 (Box 1)
      - National Republican Presidential Convention (Chicago, IL), 1960 July 23-29; D2090 (Box 1)
      - Press Conference - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Nixon man (55th St.), 1960 August 2; D2092 (Box 1)
      - LIRR Strike Settlement - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Mayor Wagner Press Conference (55th St.), 1960 August 3; D2093A (Box 1)
      - Swear-In (55th St), D2093B (Box 1)
      - Swear-In - Commissioner Sam Aldrich (youth) (55th St.), 1960 September 1; D2095 (Box 1)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Ambassador & Mrs. Lodge leave hotel to begin campaign (Waldorf Towers), 1960 September 3; D2097 (Box 1)
      - Labor Day tour of Beaches - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Lodge (Jones Beach, Rockaway, Coney Island), 1960 September 5; D2098 (Box 1)
      - Agricultural Dinner - Chamber of Commerce (Syracuse, NY), 1960 September 7; D2099 (Box 1)
      - NYS Fair (Syracuse, NY), 1960 September 8; D2100 (Box 2)
      - National Urban League Dinner (Commodore Hotel), 1960 September 8; D2101 (Box 2)
      - Walking Tour - Nelson A. Rockefeller & John Lindsey (NY City), 1960 September 20; D2102 (Box 2)
      - Hobson Reynolds - Negro Elks (55th St.), 1960 September 21; D2103 (Box 2)
      - Telephone Pioneers (Madison Square Garden), 1960 September 21; D2104 (Box 2)
      - Ogdensburg Bridge (St. Lawrence), 1960 September 27; D2105 (Box 2)
      - Ogdensburg Rotary (Ogdensburg Armory), 1960 September 27; D2106 (Box 2)
      - Harpur College Dedication (Binghamton, NY), 1960 September 29; D2108 (Box 2)
      - Howard Jones, Wm. Rand, Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St.), 1960 October 7; D2112 (Box 2)
      - Nixon - Ike Rally (Coliseum), 1960 November 2; D2117 (Box 2)
      - Loring Electric Dedication of New Building (Bronx), 1960 November 3; D2118 (Box 2)
      - Bob MacCrate (Albany), 1960 November 28; D2120 (Box 2)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Press Conference (Albany), 1960 November 28; D2121 (Box 2)
      - Malcom Wilson & World's Fair Committee (55th St.), 1960 December 1; D2122 (Box 2)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller official pictures (55th St.), 1960 December 3; D2123 (Box 2)
      - D2128 (Box 2)
      - D2132 (Box 2)
      - D2134 (Box 2)
      - D2135 (Box 2)
      - D2620 (Box 2)
      - D2644 (Box 2)
    - Prints, 1961 January-July; D3040-D3054
      - 150th Anniversary of the NY Public Library (NY City), 1961 May 23; D3040 (Box 2)
      - Louis Lefkowitz and Nelson A. Rockefeller and Civil Rights Groups (55th St), 1961 May 28; D3044 (Box 2)
      - Louis Lefkowitz Rally at Coliseum (Coliseum), 1961 June 23; D3053 (Box 2)
      - Binghamton Regional Development Tour (Binghamton), 1961 July 13; D3054 (Box 2)
    - Prints, 1962 January-December; D4024-D4112
      - Ithaca Odd Fellows organization; youth rehabilitation ground-breaking ceremony (Ithaca), 1962 June 2; D4024 (Box 2)
      - Albany Stairs (Albany), 1962 June 26; D4029 (Box 2)
      - 250th Anniversary Celebration - Saratoga Spa opening & dedication of new park & recreation center (Schoharie), 1962 June 30; D4032 (Box 2)
      - Nassau-Suffolk, LI counties Regional Development Tour (Nassau/Suffolk), 1962 July 17-19; D4035 (Box 2)
      - Malone- Poughkeepsie Fair (Malone/Poughkeepsie), 1962 August 22-23; D4047 (Box 2)
      - Chatham-Columbia County Fair (Chatham/Columbia), 1962 September 3; D4050 (Box 2)
      - D4104 (Box 2)
      - D4112 (Box 2)
    - Prints, 1963 January-December; D5001-D5052
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Emancipation Proclamation Sunday lay sermon at Salem Methodist Episcopal Church (129th St., 7th Ave), 1963 January 6; D5001 (Box 2)
      - Pocantico Hills & reception for President Betancourt, Venezuela (Pocantico Hills), 1963 February 22; D5005 (Box 2)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller in Red Room, press conference Legislature in session (Red Room - Albany), 1963 March 25; D5013 (Box 2)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Division for Youth Meeting (Carnegie Building), 1963 April 17; D5016 (Box 2)
      - Happy and Nelson A. Rockefeller leave for Venezuela (Idlewild), 1963 May 5; D5020 (Box 2)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Press Conference - Red Room (Red Room-Albany), 1963 June 4; D5022 (Box 2)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Press Conference on Richard Aldrich (55th St.), 1963 June 10; D5023 (Box 2)
      - Courtesy call on President Radhakrishnan of India (Hotel Carlyle), 1963 June 10; D5024 (Box 2)
      - Cattaraugus County groundbreaking for atomic repossessing plant (Buffalo), 1963 June 13; D5025 (Box 2)
      - Dedication of new wharf & terminal building of Port of Oswego Authority; Alroll plant tour & opening (Geneva, NY), 1963 June 21; D5028 (Box 2)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller press conference on Civil Rights (Hotel Dor), 1963 July 19; D5034 (Box 2)
      - NYS. Fair - also Red Room Swear In, new secretary of state John Lomenzo (Syracuse), 1963 August 28; D5037 (Box 2)
      - Worlds Fair-Port Authority Bldg. Nelson A. Rockefeller helicopter flight to/from NY City - Robert Moses, Huges of N.J. (World's Fairgrounds), 1963 October 16; D5044 (Box 2)
      - Uniformed Fireman's Association Dinner-George Meany (NY Hilton- NY City), 1963 October 28; D5047 (Box 2)
      - AFL - CIO National Convention - Nelson A. Rockefeller speaks (Americana - NY City), 1963 November 14; D5052 (Box 2)
    - Prints, 1964 January-December; D6001-6033
      - Opening of Legislature - Nelson A. Rockefeller speech (Albany), 1964 January 8; D6001 (Box 2)
      - California Trip (San Francisco, L.A.), 1964 January 28-30; D6003; Large Print (Box 2)
      - California Trip (San Francisco, L.A.), 1964 January 28-30; D6003; Small Print (Box 4)
      - California Trip (San Francisco, L.A.), 1964 January 28-30; D6003; Oversized Print (Box 8)
      - Swear Ins - Mario Biaggi & F. William Guma by Secretary of State John Lomenzo (270 Broadway), 1964 January 30; D6004 (Box 2)
      - Swear Ins - meetings (cemetery board) & Secretary of State, John Lomenzo (270 Broadway), 1964 January 31; D6006 (Box 2)
      - Opening of "Rockefeller for President" HQ (521 Fifth), 1964 February 5; D6008 (Box 2)
      - Washington, DC - Oregon trip (Washington/Portland Medford/Roseburg/Salem), 1964 February 6-8; D6009; Large Print (Box 2)
      - Washington, DC - Oregon trip (Washington/Portland Medford/Roseburg/Salem), 1964 February 6-8; D6009; Small Print (Box 4)
      - New Hampshire trip (New Hampshire), 1964 February 19-22; D6011; Large Print (Box 2)
      - New Hampshire trip (New Hampshire), 1964 February 19-22; D6011; Small Print (Box 4)
      - Women's campaign group. L-R top: Mrs. Ethan A Hitchcock, Mrs. Keene L Katz, Mrs. Laurence Rockefeller, Mrs. Keith McHugh (Rep. Nat. Committeewoman for NYS. L-R bottom: Mrs. Ogden Reid, Mrs. Lyle Carter, Mrs. Tourtellotte (Nat. Chrmn of Women for Rockefeller) (521 Fifth), 1964 February 25; D6013 (Box 2)
      - New Hampshire Trip 2 (New Hampshire), 1964 March 4-8; D6014; Large Print (Box 2)
      - New Hampshire Trip 2 (New Hampshire), 1964 March 4-8; D6014; Small Print (Box 5)
      - New Hampshire Trip 2 (New Hampshire), 1964 March 4-8; D6014; Oversized Print (Box 8)
      - New Hampshire Election Night (521 Fifth), 1964 March 10; D6015 (Box 2)
      - California Trip (California), 1964 March 11-14; D6016; Large Print (Box 3)
      - California Trip (California), 1964 March 11-14; D6016; Small Print (Box 6)
      - California Trip (California), 1964 April 1-2; D6017; Large Print (Box 3)
      - California Trip (California), 1964 April 1-2; D6017; Small Print (Box 6)
      - Oregon Trip (Oregon), 1964 March 30-31; D6017A (Box 3)
      - Detroit Trip (Detroit), 1964 April 6; D6018 (Box 3)
      - Baltimore & Washington, DC (MD, Washington DC), 1964 April 8-9; D6019 (Box 3)
      - Rockefeller Center (plaque & building) (Rockefeller Center), 1964 April 14-16; D6020; Large Print (Box 3)
      - Rockefeller Center (plaque & building) (Rockefeller Center), 1964 April 14-16; D6020; Oversized Print (Box 8)
      - Oregon (4/17), Palm Springs (4/18-9) S. California (4/20), New Orleans (4/21) (West Coast/ Louisiana), 1964 April 17-21; D6021; Large Print (Box 3)
      - Oregon (4/17), Palm Springs (4/18-9) S. California (4/20), New Orleans (4/21) (West Coast/ Louisiana), 1964 April 17-21; D6021; Small Print (Box 6)
      - Eisenhower with Nelson A. Rockefeller at Palm Springs (Palm Springs), 1964 April 19; D6022 (Box 3)
      - World's Fair New York Day (World's Fairgrounds), 1964 April 23; D6024 (Box 3)
      - NY City Ballet (Lincoln Center), 1964 April 23; D6025 (Box 3)
      - Oregon (4/27-28) California (4/29) West Virginia (4/30-5/1) (West Coast/ W. Virginia), 1964 April 27-May 1; D6026; Large Print (Box 3)
      - Oregon (4/27-28) California (4/29) West Virginia (4/30-5/1) (West Coast/ W. Virginia), 1964 April 27-May 1; D6026; Small Print (Box 6)
      - California Testimonial Pix Oregon - final campaigning Northern California, Oregon (S. & N. Calif., Oregon), 1964 May 6-15; D6027; Large Print (Box 3)
      - California Testimonial Pix Oregon - final campaigning Northern California, Oregon (S. & N. Calif., Oregon), 1964 May 6-15; D6027; Small Print (Box 6)
      - California Testimonial Pix Oregon - final campaigning Northern California, Oregon (S. & N. Calif., Oregon), 1964 May 6-15; D6027; Small Print (Box 7)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller at Headquarters - with press (521 Fifth), 1964 May 16; D6028 (Box 3)
      - Meeting with Romney at W.F. (World's Fair), 1964 May 18; D6029 (Box 3)
      - California Campaigning (California), 1964 May 19; D6030; Large Print (Box 3)
      - California Campaigning (California), 1964 May 19; D6030; Small Print (Box 7)
      - Election night (521 Fifth), 1964 June 2; D6030A (Box 3)
      - California Press Conference (521 Fifth), 1964 June 3; D6030B (Box 3)
      - NY Republican State Com. (Ten Eyck - Albany), 1964 June 11; D6031 (Box 3)
      - Meeting - Chancellor Erhard (Waldorf Hotel), 1964 June 11; D6032 (Box 3)
      - Press Conference - Scranton (521 Fifth), 1964 June 16; D6033 (Box 3)
  - Contact Sheets, 1959-1964
    - Contact Sheets, 1959 June-December; D100-D214
      - Lions Club (Madison Square Garden), 1959 June 30; D100 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Joint Session of Legislature (Albany), 1959 July 1; D101 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Arbor Day Life - Malcolm Wilson & Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St.), 1959 July 2; D102 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Westchester Magazine - Malcolm Wilson & Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St.), 1959 July 2; D103 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - NAACP 50th Annual Convention (Coliseum - NY City), 1959 July 13; D104 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - 10-Mile River Boy Scout Camp (Monticello, NY), 1959 July 28; D105 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - National Association of State Budget Officers-Dr. Hurd, David Coltrane, Budget Director, NC (Barbizon Plaza), 1959 August 19; D106 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Governor's Day at Jones Beach (Jones Beach), 1959 August 20; D107 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Departure for Norway (Idlewild Airport), 1959 August 20; D108 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Steve and Ann arrive in Idlewild (Idlewild Airport), 1959 August 24; D109 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Harness Racing Commission Appointment - J. Farley, S. Eddy, R. Glasser (55th St.), 1959 August 24; D110 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Eleanor Harris and Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St.), 1959 August 26; D111 (Box 9, Folder 1)